Hello.
In this next lecture, I'm going to go over some websites I'd like to use to find cool 2D assets for
my games.
The first one is Itch.io.
To find assets on this website, go to browse games, then go game development and then select assets.
You can then filter by tag by what type of assets you want to find.
So if I go to DD, it's only going to show me to the assets and I can filter by more things such as
free on sale or paid.
So let's scroll down H to IO has loads of cool 2D free assets.
The other website I like to use is open game or org.
We can just go browse and select 2D art and everything on this website is completely free.
Again, I think it has like hundreds of free assets that you can use.
And the final place you can find two RD assets is the marketplace.
There aren't too many two RD assets on the marketplace, but the awesome I know graphic tune studio,
they've created a bunch of two RD assets and I think there are a couple more, but there aren't really
as many on the marketplace.
But there are loads on Instagram and open game on the org.